PARK JU HYUN
PARK YONG WOO
KANG HOON
HUNTER WITH A SCALPEL
PLACES, COMPANIES, FIGURES, ORGANIZATIONS,
BACKGROUND, SETTING,
CASE, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL ONLY
CHILDREN AND ANIMAL ACTORS UNDER THE
SUPERVISION OF GUARDIANS AND EXPERTS
Yoon.
YOON
Se-eun.
YOON SE EUN
Now it's yours.
From now on, write down the food or
the thing you want in this book.
I'll buy it for you later.
But, you have to write
picture diary.
What is a diary?
Write what you did on the day
that and happy or sad things like that.
EUN SEO
PLAYING WITH EUN-SEO
Yoon Se-eun, why?
The background is all red?
Later the red color will run out.
Use other colors too.
Give. I have to
coloring this side too.
Does it have to be red?
What's this?
The sea.
What?
Who is the person who colors the sea?
In red?
Look.
More like the sea than
wear red, right?
HUNTER WITH A SCALPEL
EPISODE SEVEN
LEE YEON JU
YOON SE EUN
YONGCHEON JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL
I remember!
No wonder I feel familiar
while paying attention to it.
Isn't this eye shape
similar to Doctor Seo?
You're such a jerk!
Ignore the eye shape and center
That face is the nose, right?
Her nose is very different.
Why can't a criminal detective like you have
a talent for recognizing at first sight?
For the time being, the selection
first we are...
a woman in her 30s who lives in the city
Yongcheon and similar to this photo.
So, we are looking for a child
the one that was lost first, right?
Chairman Jung?
Yes.
We prioritize that
because this is a 2003 photo.
Montage spread today?
Yes, the relief team went
and the old town area is finished.
New city area team
will also be completed today.
Let's just accept the montage report first.
Who knows, we might get big results.
Yes, come on.
Are there no results yet from
yesterday's checkup?
The relationship between victims
increasingly non-existent.
There are no work
relations or acquaintances.
The first and third victims
have the same financial records.
In which part?
Min-guk's laundry.
Seok-woo, stay there.
Let me beat you up!
He just wanted to dry clean.
If you have a problem with that, everyone
Yongcheon case by Min-guk.
Come on, let's move.
Then if you see someone who looks like you
montage, check his identity.
- Understand?
- Yes.
Chairman Jung and I will
stop by Min-guk's place.
Who knows we might get it
good information again.
3D MONTAGE CREATION RESULTS
Yoon Se-eun.
It will all be damaged.
Do you want me to teach you too?
Put the cloth together...
and in turn you insert the
needle into the fabric like this.
Finish with a ribbon knot.
Finished.
Looks perfect
sewn like this, right?
Doesn't look like
separated, right?
Be careful playing it.
I'll be mad if it tears again.
Eun-seo, come back
go to your room and study.
Yes, Dad.
I'll come again later.
Don't be lazy and practice.
We'll be going out on duty soon.
So what happened to Eun-seo?
You killed him?
Don't pull your hand away
when bitten by a dog.
But push deeper.
His mouth will open
and let go of your hand.
It is here.
Block 203, number 802.
Pink blouse, 20,000 won.
Taken live February 13th.
CHOI MIN-GUK (YONGCHEON BANK)
You are right. After
he's not coming anymore?
Yeah, I didn't see it.
When delivering clothes, are there any contents?
His rather strange phone conversation...
or maybe come with someone
something a bit suspicious like that?
I'm not sure either.
It seems like he came twice
alone and not talking to others.
Large apartments are in the new city area.
Are your customers from there too?
That's because my laundry...
His laundry is the best here.
That's why we have so many customers.
It's not like that.
Hyuk-geun was very surprised when
wash your pants at your laundry.
I see, your feet are a little comfortable.
About this?
Very obvious, huh?
He had an accident.
Anyway, thank you.
Have taken the time.
It doesn't matter.
Just come anytime if there is a problem.
Thank You.
What is that space?
LAUNDRY ROOM
Laundry room.
Can I see it?
Yes?
Why did you come here?
Let's just go.
It's okay. My place.
Open to you.
Please take a look around.
Base.
Forgive me.
It's okay, it's natural.
See, right?
Yongcheon Middle School.
YOON SE EUN
YONGCHEON JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL
WE NEED INFORMATION
PHOTO FIRST, FACE SKETCH NOW
Sorry, Min-guk.
If someone is at a dead end, they will
definitely so no matter what he does.
There are times when I am also very
want to teach him a lesson.
It's okay, he must be curious too.
MY WIFE
I'll take a call first.
Yes.
Hello, are you done?
You've tried. How are you?
Nothing's wrong, right?
This place is old.
I'm embarrassed to show it.
I put together what I
could just to find food.
No, thank you for your cooperation.
Yes, whenever you need.
WE NEED INFORMATION
PHOTO FIRST, FACE SKETCH NOW
What is it?
What is he doing?
We just came to ask. Why
to the point of searching his workplace?
Even though this is in the city, it's
different from in Seoul. Rumors spread quickly.
Later you buy a drink and meet him.
Apologize and say it honestly.
Senior Chang Jin.
Let's try checking Choi Min-guk.
Why is our conversation
heading in that direction?
Besides the perpetrator
may know the victim...
in the laundry also usually use
lax, needles, thread, etc.
He also uses a lot of plastic items
such as buckets and brushes.
I don't know what to say.
If that's your logic,
I also need to get checked.
There are a lot of those
things in my house.
So, how about this?
Similar, right?
Isn't this person's way of walking normal?
That's right.
Geez.
- Doctor Seo?
- Geez.
We meet again after
you live here.
Correct.
Where do you want to go?
Are you hurt?
I'm a little bit stumped.
Something is stuck.
Blood?
It is nothing.
I thought you were hurt again.
Excuse me.
Doctor Seo.
We have something.
Right, I forgot.
Regarding the report
toxicology of cases one and two.
Lately I've been a bit overwhelmed just receive
verbal information without having the documents.
Can I have a copy?
That's the thing apparently.
Of course.
When should I submit it?
That...
Lately we have had to
report to the head of office.
Is it possible today?
I'll try today.
Happy working again.
Yes, be careful.
PANCURONIUM BROMIDE
PANCURONIUM CONTENT 5.6µG/ML
NOT DETECTED
NUMBER HIDDEN
Already home?
What do you want?
Dad should be the one asking that.
Do you really mean to kill me?
You have no right to talk like that.
After shocking me with electricity.
If not so...
My daughter who has not been seen for a long
time I met him about to stab his father.
Can't Dad?
Advise you as a parent?
Have you seen the montage?
What montage?
A gift from you.
Spread throughout Yongcheon.
That's it. How is it? Do you like it?
In fact, Dad can do other things too.
As you wish.
Now I am very
trouble because of you.
Don't be like this.
And we make one actor.
This is what Doctor Seo told me, right?
I thought the case was closed.
Why is it so exciting?
A drug addict?
Even though rumors have spread
if he is indeed weak, right?
What is this? "Undetected"?
I don't know who wrote it, but
This must be giving Doctor Seo a headache.
O-shaped legs.
Have you shared the montage?
- Already.
- How is the result?
Still nothing.
We have conducted a surprise inspection.
But still haven't got anything.
You guys should
I've got a little info.
By the way, regarding the case
The Blue Barrel I mentioned yesterday...
Oh my, you're up to your old tricks again.
The word "not yet" from not yet I
have already forbidden it if it is solved.
Yes, I know.
But please listen to me just once.
I think, we really
can see something.
The case has many
relevance to our case.
Frankly, we all believe it if this
is not the perpetrator's first crime.
Take a look at this.
Mutilation of 17 parts, cleaned with
lax, death due to neck fracture...
pancuronium from an injection site.
Then the suspect Go Doo-sam also has a child a girl
the same age as the child in yesterday's photo.
If there is thread and medicine,
will be exactly the same as our case.
Seok-woo, whose side are you on?
There is no bias in the investigation.
Because of that...
If we dig into this case while
investigating the girl in the photo...
we might find something...
Okay.
That makes sense too.
That makes perfect sense.
I'll leave this part to Chairman Jung.
Completely. So, just do it as freely as you like.
You are serious?
Yes.
But you can't invite anyone else.
They are already overwhelmed. It
could be a riot. if added unsolved cases.
Because this is the result of your thinking,
you just finish it at your level...
no matter how.
Then we must not be
discouraged. Understand?
We have to show that
we focus on this case now...
up to 280 thousand residents
Yongcheon can sleep soundly.
Then you, Chairman Jung.
As you have previously determined, bring
the results even if it's just a fingernail.
Oh my, damn.
Now Chairman Jung
you've felt it, right?
We have to focus on one investigation
in times of personnel shortages like this.
If you move alone like this, the ones who have
the most difficulty are your team members.
Make the perpetrator?
You still keep it
Oh Min-ho's corpse, right?
Give me the body and organs.
I will make the perpetrator with
implanting someone else's DNA.
All these things you do...
I can sort everything out well.
Do you want to fix it?
Why my daughter Se-eun
so changed your mind?
This wouldn't have happened if you hadn't
put my photo inside the corpse.
So, let's get this sorted out.
We sorted everything out like it never happened.
Happened and start again with a new one.
Okay.
I will prepare the perpetrator.
There are people anyway
targeted by the police.
If you can get it
a little DNA from that person's house...
I'll put it in
body parts and throw them away.
Then you autopsy him and all
finished once the suspect is identified.
This is made more exciting by the doctor
the forensics is my own daughter.
Dad also prepared the car.
You just warm up your body first.
JUNGANG ROAD 1, 124, TAEYANG VILLA
SEO SE HYUN
TWO FILES OF DRUG TEST REPORTS
DRUG TEST REPORT_OH MIN-HO
DRUG TEST REPORT ON CORPSES
Not detected.
NAM SEUNG HYUP
"NOT DETECTED"
THE MYSTERY OF NAM'S DEATH
SEUNG HYUP
THERE IS A LOT OF EVIDENCE,
BUT "UNDETECTABLE"?
Are you alright?
Contact me whenever you need help.
JUNGANG-RO ROAD-1
My daughter, have you arrived?
HAS MY DAUGHTER ARRIVED?
It's so noisy.
Dad forgot. Dad didn't have time.
Clean up the rest.
Please help me.
What's this?
The equipment belongs to Dad.
Use it as much as you like.
He's looking at everything.
That bastard.
Se-eun.
It is time.
Yes.
Damn it. Who are you?
Who are you to try to kill me?
Who sent you?
Who are you?
I think I've seen you before.
You who appeared on television...